<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EICP-LAB</title>
    <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on EICP-LAB</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 01:29:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://eicp-lab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CNCC Green Bag</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/12/12/cncc-green-bag-12-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 01:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/12/12/cncc-green-bag-12-12/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PhD student Yang Zhang participated in CNCC Green Bag and delivered a talk about “Solar photovoltaic integration in mining regions:evaluating global energy potential and benefits to sustainability&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic seminar</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/12/09/academic-seminar-12.9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 10:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/12/09/academic-seminar-12.9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yong Geng from the School of Environmental Science and Engineering at Shanghai Jiao Tong University was invited to give a seminar about National Nature Science Foundation Project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Trip</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/12/06/visit-offshore-wind-power-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/12/06/visit-offshore-wind-power-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu, Phd student Jiao Xiong, Yang Zhang and Yafei Xu visited the offshore wind power projects at Putian city from December 6th to 8th.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic SEMINAR</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/28/academic-seminar11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/28/academic-seminar11-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu  was invited by INET Oxford to give an online seminar titled “Raining on Bonds: The Financing Costs on Urban Investment Bonds&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNCC Green Bag</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/28/cncc-green-bag-11-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/28/cncc-green-bag-11-28/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PhD student Zhenhuan Yang participated in CNCC Green Bag and delivered a talk about “Raining on Bonds: The Financing Costs of Extreme Rain on Urban Investment Bonds&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Borui WEI</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/wbr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/wbr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;alumni&#34;&gt;Alumni&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;emailboris1843649077gmailcom&#34;&gt;Email：boris1843649077@gmail.com&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Borui WEI was a research assistant in the Energy Infrastructure and Climate Policy Lab. He got the Master’s degree in Applied Economics at Toulouse School of Economics and the Bachelor’s degree in Economics also from Toulouse School of Economics. His research interests include environmental economics, public economics and statistics. he was engaged in the area about the renewable energy economics, focusing on offshore wind energy.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chenglin Li</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/lcl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/lcl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;phd-student&#34;&gt;PhD student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;emailchenglinliconnecthkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email：chenglin.li@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chenglin Li is a PhD student in the Innovation, Policy, and Entrepreneurship (IPE) Thrust at HKUST(GZ). He holds a Master’s degree of Management Science in Public Administration from Sun Yat-sen University and a Bachelor’s degree of Management in Public Administration from Lanzhou University. His research explores the effectiveness and social impacts of energy and climate policies using quantitative methodologies. Currently, he is focusing on China’s low-carbon energy transition through the lens of just transition.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jiao Xiong</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/xj/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/xj/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;phd-student&#34;&gt;PhD student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;email-jxiong481connecthkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jxiong481@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&#34;&gt;jxiong481@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jiao Xiong is a second-year PhD student in the Innovation, Policy, and Entrepreneurship (IPE) and the Carbon Neutrality and Climate Change (CNCC) Thrust at The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou). She holds a Master’s degree in Economic Geography from the Institute of Geographic Sciences and Natural Resources Research at the Chinese Academy of Sciences, and completed her Bachelor’s degree in Economics at the Central University of Finance and Economics. Jiao’s research focuses on the transition of fossil fuel infrastructure, with a particular emphasis on offshore wind technology and clean energy finance and policy. Her work has been published in leading journals, such as Energy Policy and Energy. Recent publications include studies on the geographic distribution and economic impacts of photovoltaic poverty alleviation in China, the competitive evolution of photovoltaic power generation, and China’s cross-border energy relationships within the &amp;ldquo;Belt and Road&amp;rdquo; framework.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qing Huang</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/hq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/hq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-assistant&#34;&gt;Research Assistant&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;emailhuangqing1ucasseducn&#34;&gt;Email：huangqing1@ucass.edu.cn&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Qing Huang is a research assistant in the Energy Infrastructure and Climate Policy Lab. She is currently pursuing a Master’s degree in Economics at the University of Chinese Academy of Social Sciences and holds a Bachelor’s degree in Management from Guangdong University of Foreign Studies. Her research interests include innovation and entrepreneurship, the Chinese economy, environmental economics, and applied microeconomics. Her work has been published in journals such as Land Use Policy and Science Research Management. Currently, she is engaged in the area about the impacts of environmental regulation, foreign technology restrictions and generative AI.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siyuan Fan</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/fsy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/fsy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;mphil-student&#34;&gt;Mphil student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;emailsfan784connecthkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email：sfan784@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Siyuan FAN is a second-year MPhil student in Innovation, Policy, and Entrepreneurship Thrust at The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou). She holds a Master of Science degree in Business Analysis from The Chinese University of Hong Kong and a Bachelor’s degree in Financial Management (Financial Engineering) from Hunan University. Her current research focuses on climate change and urban resilience, employing a combination of econometrics and AI methodologies, including the use of large language models and other advanced techniques.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xin LI</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/lx/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/lx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;mphil-student&#34;&gt;MPhil Student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;email-xli464connecthkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:xli464@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&#34;&gt;xli464@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Xin LI is a second-year MPhil student in the Innovation, Policy, and Entrepreneurship Thrust at The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou). She holds a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Internet and New Media from the School of Communication and Design at Sun Yat-sen University. Before embarking on her academic journey, Xin accumulated extensive experience and demonstrated professional expertise in user research and user interface design during her six-year tenure at Tencent and Bytedance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yafei Xu</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/xyf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/xyf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;research-assistant&#34;&gt;Research Assistant&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;email15533505392163com&#34;&gt;Email：15533505392@163.com&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yafei Xu is a research assistant in the Energy Infrastructure and Climate Policy Lab. She got the Bachelor’s degree in management from Northeastern University and the Master’s degree at Lanzhou University. Her research interests include environmental economics. Her work has been published in journals such as Science of the Total Environment  and Journal of Hazardous Materials. Currently, she is engaged in the area about the energy transition and energy economics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yang Zhang</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/zy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/zy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;phd-student&#34;&gt;PhD student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;emailyzhang481connecthkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email：yzhang481@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zhang Yang is a PhD student in the IPE&amp;amp;CNCC thrust. He holds a Bachelor’s degree in Environmental Ecological Engineering from Dalian University of Technology and a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Environmental Science, jointly awarded by the Chinese Academy of Sciences and the University of Copenhagen. His research focuses on climate change, energy transitions, and the transformation of fossil fuel infrastructures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yangsiyu Lu</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/lysy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/lysy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;group-lead&#34;&gt;Group Lead&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;email-yangsiyuluhkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:yangsiyulu@hkust-gz.edu.cn&#34;&gt;yangsiyulu@hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yangsiyu Lu is an assistant professor at the Carbon Neutrality and Climate Change Thrust and the Innovation, Policy, and Entrepreneurship Thrust. She holds a Ph.D. in Environmental Economics from the University of Oxford, a M.E. in Energy and Environment from IMT Mines Albi (France), and a M.E. and a B.E. in Environmental Science and Engineering from Shanghai Jiao Tong University. Before joining HKUST(GZ), she worked as a research fellow at the Paris School of Economics and Boston University.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zhenhuan Yang</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/yzh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/team/yzh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;phd-student&#34;&gt;PhD student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;emailzyang789connecthkust-gzeducn&#34;&gt;Email：zyang789@connect.hkust-gz.edu.cn&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zhenhuan Yang is a second-year PhD student at The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Guangzhou), where he specializes in the Innovation, Policy, and Entrepreneurship Thrust (IPE) and the Carbon Neutrality and Climate Change Thrust (CNCC). He holds a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Statistics from Hunan University and a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Applied Statistics from Anhui Agricultural University. Prior to joining the EICP lab, Zhenhuan served as a research assistant at the School of Management, University of Science and Technology of China (USTC). His research primarily focuses on the causal relationship between climate change and economic outcomes, with a special emphasis on the consequences of extreme weather events. Recently, his work has examined the impact of extreme weather on government behavior.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic SEMINAR</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/18/academic-seminar11-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/18/academic-seminar11-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Mengmeng Guo from the School of Finance at Nanjing Agricultural University was invited to give a seminar titled “Flooded Venture: Extreme Rainfall and Entrepreneurship” at HKUST (GZ) and to participate in our group meeting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xiangzhang economic academic workshop</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/16/xiangzhang-economic-academic-seminar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/16/xiangzhang-economic-academic-seminar/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PhD student Jiao Xiong attended the Xiangzhang Economic Academic Workshop, where she delivered a talk titled &amp;ldquo;Technological Change from Fossil Fuels to Renewables: Evidence from Offshore Energy&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greater Bay Area Science Forum</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/15/greater-bay-area-science-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/15/greater-bay-area-science-forum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu attended the 2024 Greater Bay Area Science Forum&amp;rsquo;s Green Energy Industry Science and Technology Innovation Sub-Forum and visited the Big Data Center for Guangdong Offshore Wind in Yangjiang City.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNCC Green Bag</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/14/cncc-green-bag/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 21:29:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/14/cncc-green-bag/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PhD student Jiao Xiong participated in CNCC Green Bag and delivered a talk about “Technological change from fossil-fuel to renewable: Evidence from offshore energy”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World AI for Science Competition</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/10/visitng11-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/10/visitng11-10/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu was invited to serve as a judge for the social science track of the 2nd World AI4S Prize.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ENERGY TRANSITION AND CLIMATE FINANCE WORKSHOP</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/09/symposium-on-energy-transition-and-climate-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/09/symposium-on-energy-transition-and-climate-finance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu was invited to attend the workshop on “Sustainable Future: Energy Transition and Climate Finance” in Southwestern University of Finance and Economics and give a talk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tianjin University Economics doctoral Academic Forum</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/02/the-6th-tianjin-university-economics-doctoral-academic-forum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/02/the-6th-tianjin-university-economics-doctoral-academic-forum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PhD student Zhenhuan Yang was invited to attend the 6th Tianjin University Economics Doctoral Academic Forum and make an academic report titled:Raining on Bonds: The Financing Costs of Extreme Rain on Urban Investment Bonds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERNATIONAL SOCIETY FOR ENERGY TRANSITION STUDIES ANNUAL CONFERENCE</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/01/international-society-for-energy-transition-studies-isets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/11/01/international-society-for-energy-transition-studies-isets/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu and PhD student Xiong Jiao attended the annual conference of the International Society for Energy Transition Studies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic Seminar</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/10/23/academic-seminar-10.23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:39:46 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/10/23/academic-seminar-10.23/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Pinghan Liang from the School of Government at Sun Yat-sen University was invited to deliver a lecture on the topic:Why is there so much surveillance in China? An Explanation from a Fiscal Perspective.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic Visiting</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/10/04/visit-to-paris/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/10/04/visit-to-paris/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu visited the University of Orleans and the Paris School of Economics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNCC Workshop</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/09/21/cncc-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/09/21/cncc-workshop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu attended the Carbon Pricing and Climate Change in the Data-rich World Workshop held by CNCC Trust and gave a talk titled “Raining on Bonds: The Financing Costs of Extreme Rain on Urban Investment Bonds”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global China Fellows Summit</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/07/13/global-china-fellows-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/07/13/global-china-fellows-summit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu was invited to attend the 2024 Global China Fellows Summit and speak at the policy round table.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China in the Global Economy - Kiel-Göttingen-CEPR Conference</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/06/27/china-in-the-global-economy-kiel-g%C3%B6ttingen-cepr-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/06/27/china-in-the-global-economy-kiel-g%C3%B6ttingen-cepr-conference/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu  was invited to attend the China in the Global Economy - Kiel-Göttingen-CEPR Conference and presented her work  titled &amp;ldquo;Growing the Economy with Green Regulation: Evidence from Industrial Firm Productivity in China&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The International Workshop on Regional Air Quality Management in Rapidly Developing Economic Regions</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/05/31/international-workshop-on-regional-air-quality-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/05/31/international-workshop-on-regional-air-quality-management/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu was invited to attend the 7th International Workshop on Regional Air Quality Management in Rapidly Developing Economic Regions (7RAQM), served as the host of a parallel session, and presented her work titled &amp;ldquo;Evidence from Environmental Regulation and Industrial Firm Productivity in China&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Academic Seminar</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/05/21/academic-seminar05-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:47:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/news/2024/05/21/academic-seminar05-21/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Professor Yangsiyu Lu was invited to give a seminar in the Division of Public Policy at HKUST.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;we-are-here-to-help-you&#34;&gt;We are here to help you&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you curious about something?&#xA;Please feel free to contact us, our customer service center is working for you 24/7.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEOPLE</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/people/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;leader&#34;&gt;Leader&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;../team/lysy&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://eicp-lab.github.io/img/banners/lysy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Yangsiyu Lu&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;team-info&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../team/lysy&#34;&gt;Yangsiyu Lu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;  .team-member {&#xA;    text-align: center;&#xA;    margin: 20px;&#xA;    display: inline-block;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .team-photo {&#xA;  max-width: 150px;  &#xA;  max-height: 200px;  &#xA;  object-fit: contain;  &#xA;  margin-bottom: 10px;  &#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;  .team-info h3 {&#xA;    margin: 0;&#xA;    font-size: 1.2em;&#xA;  }&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;phd-student&#34;&gt;Phd Student&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;../team/xj&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://eicp-lab.github.io/img/banners/xj.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jiao Xiong&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;team-info&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../team/xj&#34;&gt;Jiao Xiong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;  .team-member {&#xA;    text-align: center;&#xA;    margin: 20px;&#xA;    display: inline-block;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .team-photo {&#xA;  max-width: 150px;  &#xA;  max-height: 200px;  &#xA;  object-fit: contain;  &#xA;  margin-bottom: 10px;  &#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;  .team-info h3 {&#xA;    margin: 0;&#xA;    font-size: 1.2em;&#xA;  }&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;../team/yzh&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://eicp-lab.github.io/img/banners/yzh.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Zhenhuan Yang&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;team-info&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../team/yzh&#34;&gt;Zhenhuan Yang&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;  .team-member {&#xA;    text-align: center;&#xA;    margin: 20px;&#xA;    display: inline-block;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .team-photo {&#xA;  max-width: 150px;  &#xA;  max-height: 200px;  &#xA;  object-fit: contain;  &#xA;  margin-bottom: 10px;  &#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;  .team-info h3 {&#xA;    margin: 0;&#xA;    font-size: 1.2em;&#xA;  }&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;../team/zy&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://eicp-lab.github.io/img/banners/zy.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Yang Zhang&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;team-info&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../team/zy&#34;&gt;Yang Zhang&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;  .team-member {&#xA;    text-align: center;&#xA;    margin: 20px;&#xA;    display: inline-block;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .team-photo {&#xA;  max-width: 150px;  &#xA;  max-height: 200px;  &#xA;  object-fit: contain;  &#xA;  margin-bottom: 10px;  &#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;  .team-info h3 {&#xA;    margin: 0;&#xA;    font-size: 1.2em;&#xA;  }&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;../team/lcl&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img src=&#34;https://eicp-lab.github.io/img/banners/lcl.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Chenglin Li&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;team-info&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../team/lcl&#34;&gt;Chenglin Li&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;  .team-member {&#xA;    text-align: center;&#xA;    margin: 20px;&#xA;    display: inline-block;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .team-photo {&#xA;  max-width: 150px;  &#xA;  max-height: 200px;  &#xA;  object-fit: contain;  &#xA;  margin-bottom: 10px;  &#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;  .team-info h3 {&#xA;    margin: 0;&#xA;    font-size: 1.2em;&#xA;  }&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://eicp-lab.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://eicp-lab.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lu, Y., Springer, C., &amp;amp; Steffen, B. (2024). Cofinancing and infrastructure project outcomes in Chinese lending and overseas development finance. World Development, 175: 106473.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
